Ronald G. Becker Collection of Charles Eisenmann Photographs
Ronald G. Becker collection of Charles Eisenmann photographs
- Charles Eisenmann cabinet cards
  - 304 - Mr. & Mrs. M.V. Bates giants and unidentified man (Box 4)
  - 305 - Mr. & Mrs. M.V. Bates giants and unidentified man (Box 4)
  - 306 - Chauncy Morlan fat boy (Box 4)
  - 307 - Chauncy Morlan fat boy, duplicate of #306 (Box 4)
  - 308 - Chauncy Morlan fat boy (Box 4)
  - 309 - Chauncy Morlan fat boy (Box 4)
  - 310 - Chauncy Morlan fat boy (Box 4)
  - 311 - Chauncy Morlan fat boy (Box 4)
  - 312 - Chauncy Morlan fat boy (Box 4)
  - 313 - Chauncy Morlan fat boy (Box 4)
  - 314 - Unidentified fat boy (Box 4)
  - 315 - George James fat boy (Box 4)
  - 316 - John Robinson fat man (Box 4)
  - 317 - Unidentified fat boy (Box 4)
  - 318 - Unidentified fat boy (Box 4)
  - 319 - Amelia Hill fat girl (Box 4)
  - 320 - Amelia Hill fat girl (Box 4)
  - 321 - Carrie Akers fat girl (Box 4)
  - 322 - Ida Williams fat lady (Box 4)
  - 323 - Ida Williams fat lady (Box 4)
  - 324 - Ada Briggs fat lady (Box 4)
  - 325 - Unidentified fat lady (Box 4)
  - 326 - Unidentified fat lady, same woman as #325 (Box 4)
  - 327 - Unidentified fat lady, same woman as #325 (Box 4)
  - 328 - Unidentified fat lady, same woman as #325 (Box 4)
  - 329 - Unidentified Negro fat lady (Box 4)
  - 330 - Unidentified Negro fat lady, duplicate of #329 (Box 4)
  - 331 - Rose Leslie fat lady (Box 4)
  - 332 - Unidentified fat lady (Box 4)
  - 333 - Annie Bell fat lady (Box 4)
  - 334 - Annie Bell fat lady (Box 4)
  - 335 - Annie Bell fat lady (Box 4)
  - 336 - Annie Bell fat lady (Box 4)
  - 337 - Annie Bell fat lady (Box 4)
  - 338 - Ullie Akerstrom actress/dancer (Box 4)
  - 339 - Ullie Akerstrom actress/dancer (Box 4)
  - 340 - Ullie Akerstrom actress/dancer (Box 4)
  - 341 - Ullie Akerstrom actress/dancer (Box 4)
  - 342 - Ullie Akerstrom actress/dancer (Box 4)
  - 343 - Ullie Akerstrom actress/dancer (Box 4)
  - 344 - Ullie Akerstrom actress/dancer (Box 4)
  - 345 - Lulu Lataska actress/dancer (Box 4)
  - 346 - Lulu Lataska actress/dancer (Box 4)
  - 347 - Lulu Lataska actress/dancer (Box 4)
  - 348 - Lulu Lataska actress/dancer (Box 4)
  - 349 - Lulu Lataska actress/dancer (Box 4)
  - 350 - Lulu Lataska actress/dancer (Box 4)
  - 351 - Lulu Lataska actress/dancer (Box 4)
  - 352 - Lulu Lataska actress/dancer (Box 4)
  - 353 - Lulu Lataska actress/dancer (Box 4)
  - 354 - Lulu Lataska actress/dancer (Box 4)
  - 355 - Zoe Zobedia moss haired girl (Box 4)
  - 356 - Unidentified frizzy haired girl (Box 4)
  - 357 - Zoe Meleke frizzy haired girl (Box 4)
  - 358 - Unidentified frizzy haired girl (Box 4)
  - 359 - Mille Sa Leita frizzy haired girl (Box 4)
  - 360 - Mille Annette Rarey actress/dancer (Box 4)
  - 361 - Mille Annette Rarey actress/dancer (Box 4)
  - 362 - Maude Atkinson actress/dancer (Box 4)
  - 363 - Unidentified lady in flowered dress (Box 4)
  - 364 - Unidentified lady holding basket of flowers (Box 4)
  - 364a - Unidentified girl holding toy rifle (Box 4)
  - 364b - Kiralfy Brothers Mikado Ballet (Box 4)
  - 365 - The Adams Sisters midgets? (Box 4)
  - 366 - Unidentified boy and girl in stage costume (Box 4)
  - 367 - Andrew Mack actor? (Box 4)
  - 368 - The Chanfraus actors (Box 4)
  - 369 - Mlle. Prospetto and his pets (Box 5)
  - 370 - Bobby Berry, Joseph Hart, and George Mack actors, 1900 (Box 5)
  - 371 - Miss Dolly Barry vocalist and dancer, 1900 (Box 5)
  - 372 - Hazel Reynolds vocalist and dancer, 1900 (Box 5)
  - 373 - Unidentified girl, 1900 (Box 5)
  - 374 - Little Eva, 1900 (Box 5)
  - 375 - Unidentified girl on horse (Box 5)
  - 376 - Unidentified lady standing in front of horse (Box 5)
  - 377 - Two headed cow (Box 5)
  - 378 - Performing dogs (Box 5)
  - 379 - Circus wagon (Box 5)
  - 380 - Horse standing on hind legs (paint horse), same horse as #381, 382 (Box 5)
  - 381 - Horse standing on hind legs (paint horse), same horse as #380, 382 (Box 5)
  - 382 - Horse standing in front of house (white horse), 1892; same horse as #380, 381 (Box 5)
  - 383 - Boy with cello (Box 5)
  - 384 - Boy with cello, duplicate of #383 (Box 5)
  - 385 - Young girl (Box 5)
  - 386 - Young girl (Box 5)
  - 387 - Essie Graham miniature (Box 5)
  - 388 - Girl holding pistol (Box 5)
  - 389 - Young girl in long gown (Box 5)
  - 390 - Little Florence (Box 5)
  - 391 - Little Florence (Box 5)
  - 392 - Unidentified man (Box 5)
  - 392a - Nora Hildebrandt, tattooed woman (Box 5)
- Miscellaneous portraits (Box 5)
  - 393 - Unidentified lady (Box 5)
  - 394 - Unidentified lady (Box 5)
  - 395 - Unidentified lady (Box 5)
  - 396 - Unidentified girl (Box 5)
  - 397 - Unidentified man and girl (Box 5)
  - 398 - Unidentified little girl (Box 5)
  - 399 - Unidentified baby (Box 5)
  - 400 - Unidentified baby (Box 5)
  - 401 - Unidentified man (Box 5)
  - 402 - Unidentified man (Box 5)
- Charles Eisenmann unidentified photographs (Box 5)
  - 403 - Lot of 19 misc. images (Box 5)
- Frank Wendt photographs (Box 5)
  - 404 - Priamal and Sami parasitic twins (Box 5)
  - 405 - Laloo parasitic twins, 1902 (Box 5)
  - 406 - Laloo parasitic twins, 1902 (Box 5)
  - 407 - Laloo parasitic twins, 1892 (Box 5)
  - 408 - Adolph Rudolph Siamese twins (Box 5)
  - 409 - Adolph Rudolph Siamese twins (Box 5)
  - 410 - Adolph Rudolph Siamese twins (Box 5)
  - 411 - Millie Christine Siamese twins (Box 5)
  - 412 - Midget couple (Box 5)
  - 413 - Midget couple (Box 5)
  - 414 - Midget couple (Box 5)
  - 415 - Mlle. Coretta midget (Box 5)
  - 416 - Mlle. Coretta midget (Box 5)
  - 417 - Mlle. Coretta midget (Box 5)
  - 418 - G.W. Winner and wife midgets (Box 5)
  - 419 - G.W. Winner and wife midgets (Box 5)
  - 420 - G.W. Winner and wife midgets (Box 5)
  - 421 - Major N.G.W. Winner midget (Box 5)
  - 422 - Che Mah dwarf (Box 5)
  - 423 - Che Mah and Pearley dwarfs (Box 5)
  - 424 - Che Mah dwarf (Box 5)
  - 425 - Che Mah dwarf (Box 5)
  - 426 - Che Mah dwarf (Box 5)
  - 427 - The Wild Men of Borneo midgets (Box 5)
  - 428 - The Wild Men of Borneo midgets (Box 5)
  - 429 - The Wild Men of Borneo midgets (Box 5)
  - 430 - Princess Wee Wee midget (Box 5)
  - 431 - Princess Wee Wee midget (Box 5)
  - 432 - Chief Debro and wife dwarfs, 1903 (Box 5)
  - 433 - Chief Debro and wife dwarfs (Box 5)
  - 434 - Chief Debro and wife dwarfs (Box 5)
  - 435 - Chief Debro and wife dwarfs (Box 5)
  - 436 - Princess Tiny midget (Box 5)
  - 437 - Princess Tiny midget (Box 5)
  - 438 - Princess Tiny midget (Box 5)
  - 439 - Major Ray and wife midgets (Box 6)
  - 440 - Major Ray and wife midgets (Box 6)
  - 441 - Major Ray and wife midgets (Box 6)
  - 442 - S. Horvath midgets (Box 6)
  - 443 - Horvath midgets (Box 6)
  - 444 - Horvath midgets (Box 6)
  - 445 - Bertha Carnihan midget (Box 6)
  - 446 - Bertha Carnihan midget (Box 6)
  - 447 - Bertha Carnihan midget (Box 6)
  - 448 - Bertha Carnihan midget (Box 6)
  - 449 - Little Helen Boughton midget (Box 6)
  - 450 - Unidentified midget couple (Box 6)
  - 451 - Unidentified midget couple (Box 6)
  - 452 - Capt. Jack Barnett midget (Box 6)
  - 453 - Capt. Jack Barnett midget (Box 6)
  - 454 - Capt. Jack Barnett midget (Box 6)
  - 455 - Capt. Jack Barnett midget (Box 6)
  - 456 - Prince Otto midget (Box 6)
  - 457 - Major J. Rihnback midget (Box 6)
  - 458 - Major Mite midget (Box 6)
  - 459 - Little Russian Prince midget (Box 6)
  - 460 - Little Russian Prince midget (Box 6)
  - 461 - Little Russian Prince midget (Box 6)
  - 462 - Jenny Reynolds midget (Box 6)
  - 463 - The Giant Hugo and unidentified midget (Box 6)
  - 464 - Unidentified giant man (Box 6)
  - 465 - Unidentified giant man (Box 6)
  - 466 - Louis Moilanen giant (Box 6)
  - 467 - Louis Moilanen giant (Box 6)
  - 468 - Louis Moilanen giant (Box 6)
  - 469 - Capt. S.A. Shields and wife giants (Box 6)
  - 470 - Unidentified giant lady (Box 6)
  - 471 - Baby Adelina fat girl (Box 6)
  - 472 - Unidentified fat girl (Box 6)
  - 473 - Chauncy Morlan and wife fat people (Box 6)
  - 474 - Unidentified fat lady (Box 6)
  - 475 - Unidentified fat lady (Box 6)
  - 476 - Unidentified fat lady (Box 6)
  - 477 - Gertie Plath fat lady (Box 6)
  - 478 - Gertie Plath fat lady (Box 6)
  - 479 - Unidentified fat lady (Box 6)
  - 480 - L.N. Monroe skeleton man, 1893 (Box 6)
  - 481 - Norman Green skeleton man, 1899 (Box 6)
  - 482 - Fred Howe fat boy and George Moore thin man (Box 6)
  - 483 - Fred Howe fat boy and George Moore thin man, duplicate of #482 (Box 6)
  - 484 - Unidentified tattooed lady (Box 6)
  - 485 - Unidentified tattooed man (Box 6)
  - 486 - Annie Jones bearded lady (Box 6)
  - 487 - Eugene Berry man with elephantitis legs (Box 6)
  - 488 - Unidentified lady with partial legs (Box 6)
  - 489 - Piebald black girls (Box 6)
  - 490 - John Owens man without arms (Box 6)
  - 491 - Charles Tripp man without arms (Box 6)
  - 492 - Charles Tripp man without arms, 1893 (Box 6)
  - 493 - Louis Wiser albino (Box 6)
  - 494 - Unidentified albino man (Box 6)
  - 495 - Unidentified albino girl (Box 6)
  - 496 - Unzie albino (Box 6)
  - 497 - Unzie albino (Box 6)
  - 498 - Miss Julene snake enchantress (Box 6)
  - 499 - Unidentified snake charmer (Box 6)
  - 500 - Unidentified snake charmer (Box 6)
  - 501 - Amy Arlington snake charmer (Box 7)
  - 502 - Amy Arlington snake charmer (Box 7)
  - 503 - Amy Arlington snake charmer (Box 7)
  - 504 - Wild man (Box 7)
  - 505 - Mungo wild man (Box 7)
  - 506 - Walter Wentworth contortionist (Box 7)
  - 507 - A.O. Bable cowboy, 1895 (Box 7)
  - 508 - Murdock Brothers jugglers (Box 7)
  - 509 - George Lavasseun strong man (Box 7)
  - 510 - George Lavasseun strong man (Box 7)
  - 511 - Bobby Leach daredevil (Box 7)
  - 512 - Bobby Leach balloonist and high diver (Box 7)
  - 513 - Fukushima's Royal Japanese Troupe (Box 7)
  - 514 - James Hardy Blondin high wire artist (Box 7)
  - 515 - W.H. Kidd Hanner aeronaut (Box 7)
  - 516 - Frank and Emma Caldwell knife throwing act, 1899 (Box 7)
  - 517 - Alexander strong man (Box 7)
  - 518 - Unidentified lady weightlifter (Box 7)
  - 519 - Three unidentified people holding chair (Box 7)
  - 520 - The Rev. Morrill twins evangelists (Box 7)
  - 521 - The Rev. Morrill twins evangelists (Box 7)
  - 522 - Weber and Fields actors (Box 7)
  - 523 - Horse with long mane (Box 7)
  - 524 - Linus II horse with long mane (Box 7)
  - 525 - Linus II horse with long mane, duplicate of #524 but sharper image (Box 7)
  - 526 - Pony with long tail and mane (Box 7)
  - 527 - Chief pony with long tail and mane (Box 7)
  - 528 - Mascot the talking horse (Box 7)
  - 529 - Elsie Sutliff and pony (Box 7)
  - 530 - Boy and ponies (Box 7)
  - 531 - Norris Brothers dog and pony show (Box 7)
  - 532Unidentified lady in costume (Box 7)
  - 533 - Unidentified girl with frizzy hair (Box 7)
  - 534 - Unidentified frizzy haired lady (Box 7)
  - 535 - Unidentified lady with lace dress (Box 7)
  - 536 - Amy Arlington (Box 7)
  - 537 - Lulu Lataska actress/dancer (Box 7)
  - 538 - Lady Attira sword walker (Box 7)
  - 539 - Unidentified girl on swing (Box 7)
  - 540 - Unidentified boy on swing (Box 7)
  - 541 - Unidentified girl (Box 7)
  - 542 - Little Marguerite (Box 7)
  - 543 - Unidentified girl standing on ladder (Box 7)
  - 544 - Baby Bernadine (Box 7)
  - 545 - Unidentified girl (Box 7)
  - 546 - Young girl (Box 7)
  - 547 - Two children (Box 7)
  - 548 - Pearl and Beatrice Alpine (Box 7)
  - 549 - Little Levey Sisters (Box 7)
  - 550 - Little Levey Sisters (Box 7)
  - 551 - Unidentified young girl (Box 7)
  - 552 - Corinne Washburn (Box 7)
  - 553 - Florence Washburn (Box 7)
  - 554 - Florence Washburn (Box 7)
  - 555 - Goldsmith Sisters (Box 7)
  - 556 - Ignace Paderewski - musician (Box 7)
  - 557 - Miller family (Box 7)
  - 558 - Miller family (Box 7)
  - 559 - Lional, the lion faced boy (Box 7)
  - 559a - Unidentified lady (Box 7)
  - 559b - Unidentified snake lady see also #1148, #1149 (Box 7)
- Ronald G. Becker collection of miscellaneous circus freak photographs
  - 560 - Bunnell's 3 headed songstress, 1875 (Box 8)
  - 561 - Group portrait of 11 circus freaks, 1865 (Box 8)
  - 562 - P.T. Barnum, 1865 (Box 8)
  - 563 - P.T. Barnum, 1865 (Box 8)
  - 564 - P.T. Barnum, 1865; from a Brady negative; published by Anthony (Box 8)
  - 565 - P.T. Barnum and midget, 1865 (Box 8)
  - 566 - Two unidentified hairy faced men, 1870 (Box 8)
  - 567 - Unidentified hairy faced man, 1870 (Box 8)
  - 568 - Moss haired girl with snake, 1870 (Box 8)
  - 569 - Mr. Crockett lion tamer, 1866 (Box 8)
  - 570 - Mr. Crockett lion tamer, 1866 (Box 8)
  - 571 - Elephants, 1868 (Box 8)
  - 572 - Elephant, 1865 (Box 8)
  - 573 - Eight footed horse, 1870 (Box 8)
  - 574 - Unidentified hunched back man, 1870 (Box 8)
  - 575 - Unidentified hunched back man, 1865 (Box 8)
  - 576 - Unidentified hunched back lady, 1870 (Box 8)
  - 577 - Blind Tom musician, 1865 (Box 8)
  - 578 - Alonzo Hiwanda, 1870 (Box 8)
  - 578a - Magician?, 1865 (Box 8)
  - 579 - Man with long beard, 1870 (Box 8)
  - 580 - Adaletta and Wallace man and woman fish, 1870 (Box 8)
  - 581 - The Wild Australian Children, 1865 (Box 8)
  - 582 - The Wild Australian Children, 1865 (Box 8)
  - 583 - Isaac Sprague and family, 1870 (Box 8)
  - 584 - Isaac Sprague, 1870 (Box 8)
  - 585 - Isaac Sprague, 1865 (Box 8)
  - 586 - Unidentified skeleton man, 1865 (Box 8)
  - 587 - Phoebe Dunn fat lady, 1865 (Box 8)
  - 588 - Mary Powers fat lady, 1865 (Box 8)
  - 589 - John Powers fat boy, 1865 (Box 8)
  - 590 - Ada Briggs fat lady, 1870 (Box 8)
  - 591 - Unidentified fat lady, 1870 (Box 8)
  - 592 - Unidentified fat lady, 1870 (Box 8)
  - 593 - Mary Morrison fat lady, 1870 (Box 8)
  - 594 - Unidentified fat lady, 1870 (Box 8)
  - 595 - Maggie Clark fat lady, 1870 (Box 8)
  - 596 - Maggie Rogers (?) fat lady, 1865 (Box 8)
  - 597 - Unidentified fat lady, 1865 (Box 8)
  - 598 - Caddie Monroe fat girl, 1865 (Box 8)
  - 599 - Madame Sherwood giant fat lady, 1865 (Box 8)
  - 600 - Madame Sherwood giant fat lady, 1865 (Box 8)
  - 601 - Sam Bishop fat boy, 1870 (Box 8)
  - 602 - Chas. Thurston fat boy, 1870 (Box 8)
  - 603 - Unidentified fat boy, 1870 (Box 8)
  - 604 - Mille Christine Siamese twins, 1870 (Box 8)
  - 605 - Mille Christine Siamese twins, 1870 (Box 8)
  - 606 - Mille Christine Siamese twins, 1870 (Box 8)
  - 607 - Mille Christine Siamese twins, 1870 (Box 8)
  - 608 - Mille Christine Siamese twins, 1865 (Box 8)
  - 609 - Mille Christine Siamese twins, 1865 (Box 8)
  - 610 - Mille Christine Siamese twins, 1866 (Box 8)
  - 611 - Unidentified four legged girl, 1865 (Box 8)
  - 612 - Unidentified Siamese twin babies, 1871 (Box 8)
  - 613 - Chang and Eng Siamese twins and family, 1865 (Box 8)
  - 614 - Chang and Eng and two children, 1865 (Box 8)
  - 615 - Chang and Eng and two children, 1865 (Box 8)
  - 616 - Chang and Eng and two children, 1865 (Box 8)
  - 617 - Chang and Eng and family, 1870 (Box 8)
  - 618 - Bearded girl 7 years old, 1870 (Box 8)
  - 619 - Bearded girl, 1865 (Box 8)
  - 619a - Bearded girl, 1879 (Box 8)
  - 619b - Bearded girl, 1870 (Box 8)
  - 620 - Unidentified bearded lady, 1865 (Box 8)
  - 621 - Amanda King bearded lady, 1865 (Box 8)
  - 622 - Madam Squires bearded lady, 1873 (Box 8)
  - 623 - Unidentified bearded lady, 1875 (Box 8)
  - 624 - Armless man, 1870 (Box 8)
  - 625 - Unidentified armless man, 1870 (Box 8)
  - 626 - Charles Tripp armless wonder, 1870 (Box 8)
  - 627 - Walter Stuart armless and legless man, 1870 (Box 8)
  - 628 - Barney Nelson armless boy, 1870 (Box 8)
  - 629 - Ann Leek armless lady, 1871 (Box 8)
  - 630 - Ella Harper Camel girl, 1870 (Box 8)
  - 631 - Ann Leek Thomson armless lady, 1870 (Box 8)
  - 632 - Eli Bowen legless man, 1865 (Box 8)
  - 633 - Eli Bowen legless man, 1865 (Box 8)
  - 634 - Eli Bowen, wife and child, 1865 (Box 8)
  - 635 - Eli Bowen, wife and child, 1870 (Box 8)
  - 636 - Irene Woodward tattooed lady, 1870 (Box 8)
  - 637 - Unidentified tattooed lady, 1870 (Box 8)
  - 638 - Unidentified tattooed man, 1875 (Box 8)
  - 639 - Unidentified tattooed man, 1875 (Box 8)
  - 640 - Frank Howard tattooed man, 1875 (Box 8)
  - 641 - Unidentified giant man, 1875 (Box 8)
  - 642 - Unidentified giant man, 1875 (Box 8)
  - 643 - Col. Ruth Goshen giant, 1865 (Box 8)
  - 644 - Col. Ruth Goshen giant, 1865 (Box 8)
  - 645 - Col. Ruth Goshen giant, 1875 (Box 8)
  - 646 - Col. Ruth Goshen giant, 1875 (Box 8)
  - 647 - Landen Middlecoff giant, 1875 (Box 8)
  - 648 - Unidentified giant man, 1875 (Box 8)
  - 649 - Chinese giant, 1870 (Box 8)
  - 650 - Capt. M.V. Bates giant, 1870 (Box 8)
  - 651 - Capt. M.V. Bates giant, 1870 (Box 8)
  - 652 - Unidentified giant lady, 1865 (Box 8)
  - 653 - Unidentified giant lady, 1865 (Box 8)
  - 654 - Anna Swan giant lady, 1865 (Box 8)
  - 655 - The Tom Thumb Wedding Series, 1865 (Box 8)
  - 661 - (Box 8)
  - 662 - Tom Thumb Wedding Group, 1865 (Box 8)
  - 663 - Lavinia and Minnie Warren midgets, 1865 (Box 8)
  - 664 - Unidentified midget lady, 1865 (Box 8)
  - 665 - Unidentified midget lady, 1870 (Box 8)
  - 666 - Lavinia Warren midget, 1865 (Box 8)
  - 667 - Lavinia Warren midget, 1865 (Box 8)
  - 668 - Minnie Warren midget, 1865 (Box 8)
  - 669 - Lavinia Warren midget, 1865 (Box 8)
  - 670 - Lavinia Warren midget, 1865 (Box 8)
  - 671 - Lavinia Warren midget, 1869 (Box 8)
  - 672 - Lavinia Warren midget, 1865 (Box 8)
  - 673 - Lavinia Warren midget, 1865 (Box 8)
  - 674 - Comm. Nutt and Minnie Warren midgets, 1865 (Box 8)
  - 675 - Comm. Nutt and Minnie Warren midgets, 1865; duplicate of #674 (Box 8)
  - 676 - Comm. Nutt and Minnie Warren midgets (Box 8)
  - 677 - Comm. Nutt and Minnie Warren midgets, 1865 (Box 8)
  - 678 - Comm. Nutt and Minnie Warren midgets, 1865; copy of Brady photo by NY Photographic Co. (Box 8)
  - 679 - Gen. Tom Thumb midget, 1865 (Box 8)
  - 680 - Tom Thumb and wife midgets, 1875 (Box 8)
  - 681 - Tom Thumb and wife midgets, 1870 (Box 8)
  - 682 - Tom Thumb and wife midgets, 1875 (Box 8)
  - 683 - Tom Thumb and wife midgets, 1865 (Box 8)
  - 684 - Tom Thumb and wife midgets, 1865; duplicate of #683 (Box 8)
  - 685 - Tom Thumb and wife midgets (Brady), 1865 (Box 8)
  - 686 - Tom Thumb and wife midgets, 1865; duplicate of #685 (Box 8)
  - 687 - Tom Thumb and wife midgets, 1865 (Box 8)
  - 688 - Tom Thumb and wife midgets, 1875 (Box 8)
  - 689 - Waino and Plutano Wild Men of Borneo, 1870 (Box 8)
  - 690 - Wild Men of Borneo, 1865 (Box 8)
  - 691 - Wild Men of Borneo, 1865 (Box 8)
  - 692 - Gen. Arivos midget, 1870 (Box 8)
  - 693 - Gen. Arivos midget, 1880 (Box 8)
  - 694 - Gen. Cardenas midget, 1875 (Box 8)
  - 695 - Gen. Grant Jr. midget, 1865 (Box 8)
  - 696 - Maj. S.E. Houghton midget, 1865 (Box 8)
  - 697 - Col. McGuire midget, 1875 (Box 8)
  - 698 - Unidentified midget, 1875 (Box 8)
  - 699 - Ge. Littlefinger midget, 1875 (Box 8)
  - 700 - Unidentified midget, 1869 (Box 8)
  - 701 - Admiral Dot midget, 1875 (Box 8)
  - 702 - Admiral Dot midget, 1870 (Box 8)
  - 703 - Admiral Dot midget, 1870 (Box 8)
  - 704 - Admiral Dot midget, 1870 (Box 8)
  - 705 - Admiral Dot midget, 1870 (Box 8)
  - 706 - Admiral Dot midget, 1870 (Box 8)
  - 707 - Admiral Dot midget, 1875 (Box 8)
  - 708 - Admiral Dot midget, 1875 (Box 8)
  - 709 - Gen. Mite midget, 1875 (Box 8)
  - 710 - Gen. Mite midget, 1875 (Box 8)
  - 711 - Comm. Nutt midget, 1865 (Box 8)
  - 712 - Comm. Nutt midget, 1865 (Box 8)
  - 713 - Comm. Nutt midget, 1865 (Box 8)
  - 714 - Comm. Nutt midget, 1865 (Box 8)
  - 715 - Comm. Nutt and Minnie Warren midgets, 1870 (Box 8)
  - 716 - Gen. Mite midget, 1870 (Box 8)
  - 717 - Two unidentified midgets boxing, 1865 (Box 8)
  - 718 - Chas. Decker midget, 1865 (Box 8)
  - 719 - Chas. Decker midget, 1865 (Box 8)
  - 720 - Chas. Decker midget, 1865 (Box 8)
  - 721 - Chas. Decker midget, 1870 (Box 8)
  - 722 - Ann Steere midget, 1875 (Box 8)
  - 723 - Col. Ruben Steere midget, 1870 (Box 8)
  - 724 - Col. Steere midget, 1870 (Box 8)
  - 725 - Col. Steere midget, 1870 (Box 8)
  - 726 - Col. Steere midget, 1870 (Box 8)
  - 727 - Col. Steere and wife, 1870 (Box 8)
  - 728 - Wm. Henry Steere midget, 1870 (Box 8)
  - 729 - Unidentified midget man, 1865 (Box 8)
  - 730 - Maj. Tot midget, 1870 (Box 8)
  - 731 - Unidentified midget and normal size man, 1870 (Box 8)
  - 732 - Unidentified midget, 1870 (Box 8)
  - 733 - Comm. Foote midget, 1865 (Box 8)
  - 734 - Gen. Mite midget, 1865 (Box 8)
  - 735 - Two unidentified midgets and normal size man, 1865 (Box 8)
  - 736 - Three midgets and normal size man, 1865 (Box 8)
  - 737 - Two unidentified midgets, 1870 (Box 8)
  - 738 - The Rice Family 3 midgets, 1870 (Box 8)
  - 739 - The Rice Family 3 midgets, 1870 (Box 8)
  - 740 - John McGuire midget, 1870 (Box 8)
  - 741 - Unidentified midget lady, 1875 (Box 8)
  - 742 - John McGuire midget, 1870 (Box 8)
  - 743 - Rebecca Myers midget, 1875 (Box 9)
  - 744 - Unidentified midget lady, 1870 (Box 9)
  - 745 - Sophia Schultz dwarf, 1875 (Box 9)
  - 746 - Unidentified midget lady, 1870 (Box 9)
  - 747 - Jenny Quigley midget, 1865 (Box 9)
  - 748 - Jenny Quigley midget, 1870 (Box 9)
  - 749 - Jenny Quigley midget, 1875 (Box 9)
  - 750 - Jenny Quigley midget, 1870 (Box 9)
  - 751 - Jenny Quigley midget, 1865 (Box 9)
  - 752 - Ella Downs midget, 1865 (Box 9)
  - 753 - Ella Downs midget, 1865 (Box 9)
  - 754 - Unidentified midget lady, 1870 (Box 9)
  - 755 - Unidentified midget lady, 1865 (Box 9)
  - 756 - Unidentified midget man and Anna Swan giant, 1865 (Box 9)
  - 757 - Unidentified midget girl, 1870 (Box 9)
  - 758 - Maj. Tot midget, 1870 (Box 9)
  - 759 - Italian midgets and family, 1870 (Box 9)
  - 760 - Italian midgets and family, 1870; duplicate of #759 (Box 9)
  - 761 - Madame Shaw midget and family, 1870 (Box 9)
  - 762 - Unidentified midget couple, 1875 (Box 9)
  - 763 - Unidentified midget lady, 1870 (Box 9)
  - 764 - Burdett Twins midgets, 1870 (Box 9)
  - 765 - Comm. Foote and Fairy Queen, 1870 (Box 9)
  - 766 - Comm. Foote and sister, 1865 (Box 9)
  - 767 - Comm. Foote and sister, 1865 (Box 9)
  - 768 - Comm. Foote and sister midgets and normal size man, 1865 (Box 9)
  - 769 - Comm. Foote and sister midgets, 1865 (Box 9)
  - 770 - Comm. Foote and sister, 1865 (Box 9)
  - 771 - Comm. Foote and sister and unidentified midget man, 1865 (Box 9)
  - 772 - Comm. Foote and sister and unidentified midget man, 1865 (Box 9)
  - 773 - Mille Owens long haired lady, 1875 (Box 9)
  - 774 - Mille Owens long haired lady, 1875 (Box 9)
  - 775 - Unidentified long haired lady, 1875 (Box 9)
  - 776 - Unidentified Sutherland Sister long hair, 1875 (Box 9)
  - 777 - Seven Sutherland Sisters long hair, 1875 (Box 9)
  - 778 - Sword Swallower lady, 1870 (Box 9)
  - 779 - Costumed couple, 1877 (Box 9)
  - 780 - Posed woman with thumb at nose, 1865 (Box 9)
  - 781 - Nellie Keeler child star, 1875 (Box 9)
  - 782 - Costumed Asian child holding fan, 1865 (Box 9)
  - 783 - Medicine man, 1875 (Box 9)
  - 784 - Cross eyed lady, 1865 (Box 9)
  - 785 - Kate Devin actress, 1865 (Box 9)
  - 786 - Mrs. J.J. Prior actress, 1865 (Box 9)
  - 787 - Marie Brown dancer, 1865 (Box 9)
  - 788 - Unidentified boy acrobat, 1870 (Box 9)
  - 789 - Unidentified boy acrobat, 1870 (Box 9)
  - 790 - Unidentified acrobats, 1875 (Box 9)
  - 791 - Unidentified young acrobats, 1870 (Box 9)
  - 792 - Billy Andrews acrobat, 1865 (Box 9)
  - 793 - Unidentified acrobat, 1865 (Box 9)
  - 794 - Unidentified lady acrobat, 1870 (Box 9)
  - 795 - Unidentified actress in costume, 1865 (Box 9)
  - 796 - Acrobats, 1865 (Box 9)
  - 797 - Lady in costume, 1870 (Box 9)
  - 798 - Lady in costume, 1870 (Box 9)
  - 799 - Child with moss hair, 1870 (Box 9)
  - 800 - Child with moss hair, 1875 (Box 9)
  - 801 - Millie Zulu Circassian girl, 1870 (Box 9)
  - 802 - Unidentified moss haired lady, 1870 (Box 9)
  - 803 - Zulida Hanover moss haired girl, 1870 (Box 9)
  - 804 - Unidentified moss haired girl, 1870 (Box 9)
  - 805 - Selena Bedar Circassian girl, 1875 (Box 9)